Growl growl!
Once upon a time, at the far reaches of space,
the minor planet Kumaria exploded.
The fragments of Kumaria that remained
became a meteor swarm that rained down upon Earth.
That swarm made the world's bears rise up together as one.
Then, they all started attacking humans.
Like, who could have seen that coming, right?
The humans then decided to build the Wall of Severance
in an attempt to drive all the bears, like us,
away from their world.
But guess what?
Silly old man-made rules don't work on bears!
Do the math, humans! Growl!
We are bears! We can't help that!
Bears eat people!
That's kind of like our thing!
And so...
From the beginning, we hated you.
But also, we loved you from the beginning as well.
All we wanted was to become true friends with you
So we had to cross the Wall
Chop, chop!
Munch-munch!
Chow-chop!
Much-munch!
Munch-munch!
Chow-chop!
Those bears!
They're eating a girl!!
ChYeahck...
Those are the transfer students!
Oh, I get it!
They've transformed!
They're only pretending to be human!
They're really bears!
Cheers!
Kirikuma!
Kirikuma Hiroshi!
Tragically, during an attack by two vicious bears, our friend Sumika Izumino lost her earthly life.
Next to speak, on behalf of the student body, Mitsuko Yurizono.
She has been kind enough to deliver the lovely Sumika's eulogy.
Sumika Izumino was a gentle person.
She regularly showed kindness to the weak and was always generous with her love.
No matter what, Sumika never lost sight of herself, bearing the open heart her name's...
Shouk!
Mitsuko, dear. Are you alright?
I'm fine. I'm sorry. I can do this.
Izumino will be remembered like a white wildflower in the fields of spring.
She was brave and sweet. She was graceful.
It can't be.
I refuse to believe my Sumika was eaten by those awful bears.
That can't be true. It's a lie!
Please forgive Kureha for not being able to come to the memorial today.
She's having a difficult time.
Poor thing.
She's lost someone important to her again.
I can't imagine how much she must be hurting.
Kureha? Did you have fun with your friend again today?
What's wrong? You seem down. Oh, please don't look so sad.
Aw, you really love her, don't you, sweetie?
It's okay. I'm sure you'll see her another time.
All you have to do is just keep wishing really hard.
No matter how hard I wish, I'll never see Sumika again.
I failed her. Why couldn't I protect my friend?
Bears are, like, the worst.
Does the Wall of Severance even do anything?
I mean, if a bear got through it...
Oh, which reminds me, I heard another girl from that same class is missing.
Are you serious? You think the bear got her, too?
Yeah, probably, but I guess it can't be official until they actually find a body.
Bears are disgusting.
ROWL!
Those girls are horrible, but they still look so tasty.
You know what's weird? That one girl, Kureha, she's not here today.
Yeah, you're right. We can't exactly target her if she refuses to show up at school.
Kureha Tsubaki has such a delicious smell. Yummy girl.
When you're being cool like this, you have a gorgeous smell, too.
Like a wild animal. It makes Lulu giddy.
Lulu just had the greatest idea ever!
Yay, Lulu! So clever!
There's no doubt about it.
Ginko Yurishiro and Lulu Yurigasaki.
Those transfer students are actually bears.
This is terrible, but what I saw at the flower bed is proof I'm right.
Mitsuko. Hey, Mitsuko. Earth to Mitsuko.
Hi, Konomi.
You're completely zoned out, Mitsuko. You've been acting weird.
I'm starting to get super worried about you.
Don't be. I'm fine.
How can you be so concerned about some random girl?
I know the truth. You're trying to get close to her.
What's so great about Kureha Tsubaki, though?
Why her?
You've got to know if you make friends with that girl, the invisible storm will attack you, too.
I don't want you to be hurt.
Now that Sumika's dead, Kureha's obviously going to be next.
Yes, I know.
Kureha will be targeted because she refused to back down on her love for Sumika.
Girls who don't follow the mood of the herd get excluded and ostracized.
That's how the system works, isn't it?
Then why bother?
Because there's more than Kureha worrying me.
What is it? You have to know by now you can tell me anything.
If you say so.
The truth is, I saw something awful the other day.
Hey there, girl!
We're the new transfer students and you can call this one Lulu!
And my name is Ginko.
Anyway, we were hoping you'd be a deer and let us stay with you.
What?
Growl!
What a cute house!
Hey, you're not using the attic, right?
We'd be fine up there if that's okay.
What are you talking about?
Ever since Ginko and Lulu moved to this town, we've had to sleep outside.
Growl!
Lulu itches all over!
What if it's too late and she already has the fleas?
Please!
Can't we at least use your bath?
There's no harm in that, is there?
Yeah, just a bath is okay.
Yay!
Negotiation successful!
Lulu is clever!
Hold on!
It's just for today, got it?
Hello?
Did you hear me, whatever your name is?
You can call Lulu Lulu!
What?
That's right, and you can call me Ginko.
I could taste tears on your cheek.
Growl, growl.
You could what?
Bathing, bathing, baths are super duper fun for Lulu.
Bubble, bubbles everywhere.
Growl, growl, growl!
Growl!
You can't stay here.
I'm sorry, but after you finish that, you both need to go.
Were you crying, growl, growl?
Of course I wasn't crying.
Growl, say what you will.
But I bet you didn't know that sad and lonely tears taste kind of sweet.
Growl, growl, growl.
Growl, this is pure heaven.
Lulu can't believe we safely invaded Kureha's house.
Who's a clever girl?
It's Lulu!
Growl!
Yeah, so anyway, once she's finished in there, I want both of you to get out.
I guess you can still take a bath, though, if you really want one.
I don't growl, growl, growl.
Fine.
What's with this girl?
She won't stop staring at me.
Then who in their right mind licks someone?
Gross.
And not to mention all that weird growl business.
What is that about?
Kureha, your love is the real thing.
I could taste it in your tears.
Your love is a true love.
Growl, growl.
I love you so much, Kureha.
And I always will.
What would you know about it?
I know.
Because my love is true, too.
There's no way!
You don't have a clue about Sumika or what she meant to me!
So don't pretend like you do!
Growl.
You're a real man.
Kureha Tsubaki, I've longed to see you.
In fact, we came here precisely for that purpose.
To see me?
But why?
Because of your smell.
Such a delicious scent.
Growl.
Oh yes, I'll show you my love.
Mitsuko, is something wrong?
Wait, what are you doing?
I want you to get away from Kureha now!
Ginko, Ginko, Yurashiro, Lulu, Yurigasaki?
I know what the two of you really are, so back off of her or else!
That's right, I saw you!
I witnessed exactly what you were doing that day!
Now get out of here!
I'm not going to let you lay a finger on Kureha, do you understand me?
Show her what you really are!
Damn it, they were too fast!
What's going on?
Mitsuko?
I'm sorry, there's no time to talk!
I've got to go after them!
This day can't get any weirder.
Hello?
Is your love the real thing?
This is a challenge from the Wall of Severance, Kureha, Tsubaki.
If your love is true, go to the roof immediately.
The bears are waiting for you.
Who is this?
What do you want from me?
Give yourself over to the bears, and your love will be approved.
What does that mean?
Answer me!
My love, approved?
Mitsuko loves her?
What's so great about that Kureha girl?
I've never seen her like this before.
I won't allow it, I won't!
Mitsuko belongs to me!
No one else can have her!
She's mine!
Kureha Tsubaki, you must be destroyed!
Chug!
I, Konami Yurikawa, will eat you!
Kuchuk!
Nasty!
Nasty girl!
Gah!
The time for judgment has come, growl, growl.
I'll never forgive those bears!
I'll ruin them!
Every one!
What flowers do you think you'll plant?
Yuri, lilies.
Lilies?
They were my mom's favorite.
Wow, they're growing so fast!
It's funny.
I've never seen them like this.
I always thought lily bulbs were just something you put in egg custards.
Silly, Sumika.
I sure hope they bloom soon.
Not long now.
Yeah.
Did you know your love is about to bloom?
My love is about to bloom?
Yes.
Your love.
My love.
Nasty girl!
I won't back down on my love!
I promised!
I'll never forgive the bears!
I'll ruin them!
Everyone!
We won!
Nasty-s-s-s-esteem.
Nasty Girl, nasty- nasty girl!
I keep missing!
What's going on?
Dead Beast!
Die!
Nasty Girl, die!
D продукты!
That thing, that monster murdered Tsumika!
I have to kill it!
Nasty Girl....
We want to eat that girl!
We want to eat her right this minute!
Discord is now in session!
Welcome to Severance Court.
Let the Yuri trial begin.
Growl.
Growl, growl.
Your Honor!
They can't!
It has been less than a week since the Bears last killed.
We must not allow them to prey on any more helpless humans.
This is obvious and blatant overeating.
Therefore, yes, they are guilty!
Objection!
What constitutes mega-hungry?
It's subjective and different for every Bear.
Sparkle!
Objection sustained.
What?
Bears follow Bear instincts.
For that is sexy.
Shaba-da-doo.
Defendant Bears, I ask you.
Do you want to be invisible?
Or would you rather eat humans?
We'll eat.
Bring on the humans!
Growl, growl!
I am now ready to declare the verdict.
Yuri, approved!
Growl, growl, growl!
Girl, growl, growl!
I, Ginkgo, am going to eat you.
eat you i can't find what i'm searching for
i can't find it i've been searching in the invisible storm
searching for what searching for it where give it to me the promised kiss
where do you that was a close one wasn't it you're okay right you're not hurt no i'm fine
i swear there were two bears though there must be another one lurking around here bears are usually
very cautious so we should be safe i doubt they'll try to attack again today but still
kareha i need you to listen to me you have to stop blaming yourself her death isn't your fault
the sad truth is sumika was just in the wrong place at the worst possible time you're wrong she's alive
i understand i promise you i do mitsuko i don't think i it's okay to let it out kareha
you have every right to cry it's only natural you were her best friend her truest friend
which is
Attention, Unit 105. We found a death bear on the Orochi-Kooka High School Access Road. I repeat...
Tsumika...
Oh, Kureha...
Your sweet love belongs to me now.
Slurp...
That delicious smell...
You're so good. I'm aching for you.
Not yet, though. Tonight is not our night.
Grouch, chomp chomp. Grouch, chomp chomp. Grouch, chomp chomp. Grouch, chomp chomp. Grouch, chomp chomp.
Still no good. Invisible girls always taste supremely invisible.
After tearing apart so many of them, I finally understand. Only the excluded ones can be truly wonderful and delicious. It's the girls who refuse to back down on love that taste like pomegranates and honey.
Their meat is the only thing that will satisfy my hunger.
Tsumika Izumino...
You tasted like a dream come true.
Soon...
The invisible storm will come soon!
Ugh, I can't wait!
Right now...
I want that girl right this minute!
Kureha Tsubaki!
Yes, I'm going to eat you very soon, Growl Growl!